IntelliJ IDEA has the ability to search
IntelliJ IDEA具有搜索功能
for and replace specific structures in
用于并替换中的特定结构
code we're going to take a look at this
代码，我们将看看这个
feature and see what it can do and when
功能并查看其功能和时间
you might use it you can find the
您可以使用它，您可以找到
structural search under edit find search
编辑下的结构搜索
structurally the easiest way to get
从结构上来说是最简单的方法
started is to look for existing
开始是寻找现有的
templates that match the sort of code
符合代码种类的模板
you're looking for there are lots of
您正在寻找有很多
standard searches we're going to search
我们将要搜索的标准搜索
for all field declarations just as an
对于所有字段声明，就像
example
例
running the search shows you all the
运行搜索将向您显示所有
fields declared in your Java code
Java代码中声明的字段
let's use find action to open the
让我们使用find动作打开
structural search this time so we don't
这次进行结构化搜索，因此我们不会
have to use the menu we can alter the
必须使用菜单，我们可以更改
predefined templates to refine our
预定义模板以完善我们的
search let's update this to look for all
搜索，让我们更新此内容以查找所有内容
final fields note that code completion
最后的字段请注意代码完成
is available here we're going to search
在这里我们要搜索
recursively through all our code we want
通过我们想要的所有代码递归
to match the case of our template values
以匹配我们的模板值的大小写
we're going to search in Java code but
我们将在Java代码中进行搜索，但是
we have the option to choose from a
我们可以选择
whole range of file types
整个文件类型
we can also define the scope to search
我们还可以定义搜索范围
in note that IntelliJ IDEA can tell us
注意IntelliJ IDEA可以告诉我们
straight away if our pattern is not
如果我们的模式不正确
found in a specific module we're going
在我们要去的特定模块中找到
to change the scope to look in just one
改变范围只看一个
single module to narrow our search focus
单个模块以缩小我们的搜索范围
now our search results show all final
现在我们的搜索结果显示所有最终的
fields in our standard Java module
标准Java模块中的字段
structural search is a very powerful
结构搜索功能非常强大
tool and we can configure some
工具，我们可以配置一些
interesting searches
有趣的搜索
this time let's look for method calls
这次让我们寻找方法调用
if we run this search just as it is it
如果我们按原样运行此搜索
will return a lot of results but not
将返回很多结果，但不会
much that's useful that's where we can
在这里我们可以做很多有用的事情
use the filters to be more specific
使用过滤器来更具体
about what we're looking for if we add a
如果我们添加一个
text filter here we can define the name
文本过滤器在这里我们可以定义名称
of the method we're looking for let's
我们正在寻找的方法
look for any call to a method called
寻找对称为的方法的任何调用
print' there's actually only one in this
打印'实际上只有一个
codebase what we really want is to find
代码库我们真正想要的是找到
all calls to any method that starts with
以任何开头的方法的所有调用
the word print structural search
文字印刷结构搜索
supports regular expressions so we can
支持正则表达式，所以我们可以
use this to change the criteria for
使用它来更改标准
method name to be any method that starts
方法名称可以是任何开始的方法
with print
带印刷
we have 96 matches here and it includes
我们这里有96个比赛，其中包括
system.out.print line a lot of them and
system.out.print行很多
also other methods like printf
还有其他方法，例如printf
we might decide to exclude printf type
我们可能会决定排除printf类型
methods that take more than one
方法不止一个
parameter so let's change our search to
参数，因此我们将搜索更改为
look for methods that only take a single
寻找只需要一个步骤的方法
parameter
参数
now we have fewer search results
现在我们的搜索结果更少了
let's assume we're doing the search
假设我们正在搜索
because we want to replace all these
因为我们要替换所有这些
calls with a logger call-in set of
使用记录器呼叫集的呼叫
system that out logger methods take only
记录器方法仅采用的系统
string values no other types so in order
字符串值没有其他类型，因此顺序
to find which methods can be replaced
查找可以替换的方法
easily with a log call we need to find
通过日志调用轻松找到我们
only the methods that are passed a
只有通过的方法
string we can do this by changing the
字符串，我们可以通过更改
type of the parameter we're searching
我们正在搜索的参数类型
for
对于
to a string
到一个字符串
now we see only print methods that take
现在我们只看到需要
a string type whether it's a literal
字符串类型，是否为文字
string or a variable of type string now
字符串或字符串类型的变量
we've refined our results we can do our
我们已经完善了我们的结果，我们可以做到
replacement using find action we can go
使用查找动作进行替换
to replace structurally which is also
在结构上取代
available from the fine menu
可以从精致菜单中获得
and we can say which code we want to
我们可以说我们想要哪个代码
replace it with if we tick these boxes
如果我们勾选这些框，请替换为
the code will be simplified and
该代码将被简化，
formatted when it goes into the file the
进入文件时格式化
replace box also has code completion and
替换框也有代码完成和
suggestions
建议
the search results gives a preview of
搜索结果提供了预览
which code will be replaced and we can
哪些代码将被替换，我们可以
either replace a single result with our
用我们的替换单个结果
new code or replace all of the results
新代码或替换所有结果
looking at this class we can see all the
看着这堂课，我们可以看到所有
print learned methods that took a string
打印采用字符串的学习方法
have been replaced with a call to log or
已被调用日志代替，或
fine
精细
but those that took objects or primitive
但是那些拿了对象或原始的东西
values have not been touched
值没有被触及
these could be replaced using a
这些可以用替换
structural search from a place that is
从一个地方进行结构搜索
more appropriate for these methods the
更适合这些方法
structural search box shows you all the
结构搜索框显示所有
searches you've performed in the past so
搜索您过去执行过的操作，因此
you can rerun any of them
您可以重新运行其中任何一个
we can also save our searches as
我们还可以将搜索保存为
templates giving them an appropriate
模板给他们合适的
name so we can use them later
名称，以便以后使用
we can find these save templates under
我们可以在下面找到这些保存模板
the user-defined section
用户定义的部分
as you can see structural search is
如您所见，结构搜索是
powerful and very configurable a good
功能强大且可配置性很好
way to understand what's possible and
理解可能的方式
figure out how to perform the searches
弄清楚如何执行搜索
you need is to look at the existing
您需要看的是现有的
templates see how the filters are
模板查看过滤器的状态
defined and experiment with changing
定义并尝试改变
them
他们
filter support text and type as we saw
如我们所见，过滤支持文本和类型
but they also support scripts which
但它们也支持脚本
provides even more flexibility as well
提供更大的灵活性
as using the structural search and
如使用结构搜索和
replace functionality as it is we can
尽我们所能替换功能
also use these search templates to
也使用这些搜索模板来
create our own custom inspections
创建我们自己的自定义检查
to do this we need to turn on the
为此，我们需要打开
general structural search inspection and
一般结构搜索检查和
configure it with either a search
通过搜索进行配置
template which will simply flag specific
模板，将仅标记特定的
code or a replace template which
代码或替换模板
suggests a replacement for the code
建议替换代码
we'll use the same template as before
我们将使用与以前相同的模板
but change it slightly to look for
但略微更改以寻找
instances that print an int when code
在代码时打印int的实例
like this is found we can replace it
像这样找到我们可以替换它
with a logger call and convert the
与记录器调用并转换
parameter to a string this new template
此新模板的字符串参数
name will be displayed when the
名称将在
inspection finds code that matches we
检查发现与我们匹配的代码
can have this inspection enabled all the
可以启用所有
time to show as much in code as we edit
是时候在我们编辑时显示尽可能多的代码了
or we can specifically run this
或者我们可以专门运行
inspection over the current module to
检查当前模块以
see where the matching code is
查看匹配的代码在哪里
as with any inspection we can either fix
与任何检查一样，我们可以修复
the code via the inspection results
通过检查结果的代码
window
窗口
or we can quick fix problems in the
或者我们可以快速解决问题
editor IntelliJ IDE is powerful
编辑器IntelliJ IDE功能强大
structural search and replace can be
结构搜索和替换可以
configured to find and replace complex
配置为查找并替换复杂
patterns in the code thanks for watching
代码中的模式感谢您的观看
you
您